- Clones.- Clones?
Well, we don't usethe c-word.
Genetic identicals.
Yeah, we count nineof us, so far.
We're like lab ratsin an illegal experiment.
It's an electrode.
It monitors
electrical activityin the brain.
Just tell me what happensto the results.
They go to Olivier.
Olivier, what are you doing here?Is something wrong?
Weneed to talk about Beth.
We need to try and behonest with each other.
I'm not doing anyof this by choice.
So they forced youto be Beth's monitor
for two years, withoutever knowing why?
I did peek.
You have killer grades.
Delphine.
Cosima. Hey, Cosima,you were right.
Paul doesn't even knowabout clones.
I may have a monitordilemma of my own.
It's me, this time.I know.
Is someone trying to hurt us?
I need you to tell mewhere I came from.
Neolution gives usthe opportunity
at self-directedevolution
and I believe that'snot only a choice,
but a human right.
Olivier called Paul inhours ago,
and he's not picking up.
Well, that isn't out ofthe ordinary, is it?
How should I know?
There's nothing normal
about any of this, is there?
Sarah, this isthe new normal, okay?
So, Paul's a monitor.
He reports to Olivier,his handler, right?
As long as Paul is on our side,
we can start to finallyget some answers.
That's my point, Cosima.
What if he's not on our side?
I mean, what if he's
selling us out right now?
Let's go back eight months,
before Beth's shooting.
We already did, Olivier.
When you first stated
"she doesn't seemto be herself."
Yeah, she began abusing
prescription drugs.
Why are you taping this?
At the time, you felt it was
a typical response
to the stresses of police work.
Do you view it any differently,
in hindsight?
No. Her declineled directly
to her civilian shooting.
She only got worse from there.
This, through your lensas a former soldier.
If you told mewhat this was about,
perhaps I could help you.
Perhaps you are helping me.
Don't do it, Cosima.
Stay away from Delphine, yeah?
Well, if we're going to
get past our monitors,we have to engage.
Yeah, look where that got me.
Into bed with him?
Okay, look whereit got Alison, yeah?
She smoked her husbandwith a golf club
on a hunch thathe was her monitor
and, now, they're awayat a couple's retreat,
trying to repairtheir marriage.
Okay, I'll obviouslyapproach Delphine
way more logically than that.
No, you won't.
Sarah, my situation is waydifferent than yours is.
Right, 'cause you're sucha brilliant scientist.
No, because she doesn'tknow that I know.
I'm the one who'smonitoring her.
Can you please juststay away from her
until I find out if Paul's
selling us down the river?
Whatever.
Got anything else we needto be paranoid about?
God, I hope not.
Tomas?
Shh, shh shh.
Where am I?
You're getting stronger.
Orphan Black 01x07Parts Developed In An Unusual Manner
Original Air Date May 11, 2013
Olivier told Paul to meet him
at an underground club he owns.
That's Paul's car, so.
What a mess.
You know, even if he's not
ratting me out in there,those medical tests
could still tell himI'm not Beth.
Cosima said they wouldn't.
Yeah, well, she'sblinded by science.
Maybe, but, from everything
I found online,
she's right.
You and Beth are clones,
so you and Bethhave identical DNA.
Identical?
Yep.
The DNA samplesfrom the Jane Doe
in the gravel crusher
and the killerin the bathroom...
A match, same person.
That doesn't make any sense.
Someone in the labmust've messed up,
contaminated ormislabeled the samples.
Not on my watch.
Then what, Janice?
I took Jane Doe DNA
from a femur.
Our suspect killer's DNA came
from blood we foundin the bathroom.
Maybe the killer plantedJane Doe's blood there.
What, so she carriesaround a couple pints
of Jane Doe's blood andjust splashes it around?
Well, that's more likelythan she walked
into my lab and tamperedwith the samples.
Maybe someone withaccess tampered.
Are you trying to turn my ulcer
into a heart attack?
No, we're missing something,
from the very beginning,on this thing.
Yeah, I.D.s.
So, if the high tech's broken,
we do it the horse-and-carriage way.
Start from the beginning,
comb through that wholeshitpile again.
Oh, where's that
damn Jane Doe facialreconstruction?
It's coming.The face went
through a friggin'gravel crusher.
"Someone with access"?
Beth would nevertamper with evidence.
Okay, maybe not,but you had questions
about her run-in withthe killer, didn't you?
Square one, like the man said.
Open minds.
We'll see what we find.
Eh, hang on.
Oh.Cybergoths.
That's interesting.
I know those people.
Enough waiting.I need to know
what Paul's up to.I'm going in.
What? No!No!
You can't go in there,
with your recognizable mug.
Besides...
Clubland is my world.
You carry that aroundwith you everywhere?
Maybe.
Well, hello.
Neolution's a private club.
I know, but you look so lonely.
Not even a little.
Oh, good.
You look a littlemore important.
I...I... I...
I've come all the wayfrom Brixton
to party at Neolutionbefore I die.
My friends told meto mention Olivier.
You're dying?
Then you're not familiar
with Neolutionism?
Oh, there'san -ism.
¢Ü centipede
augmentation?
Self-directedevolution?
I'm intrigued.
Is everyone herea Neolutionist?
No, not everyone.
We've got technoprogressives,
body mods, biohackers.
Now, wait, what about your eye?
Is that a permanentaugmentation?
It will be, one day.
I've got other enhancements.
Right.
Well, a philosophyso... physical
makes for a veryhandsome tribe.
What about Olivier?
Is he enhanced?
Darling, you have no idea.
When's the last timeyou and Beth
were sexually intimate?
Three days ago.
Who initiated it?
She did.
How would you characterize it?
¢Ü Centipede
I'm not sure I understandthe question.
Would you describe theintercourse as intimate,
aggressive,
perfunctory,
sensual?
I would say passionate.
Beth's generallya "cold fish"...
Your words.
It's hard for me to help,
if I don't knowwhat's going on.
All of this architecture...
The psychological profiling,
physical exams,social metrics...
You must know
it doesn't existfor Beth alone.
I don't assume anything.
Of course you do.You're trained...
Surveillance, intelligence,
security.
The problem withclandestine ops is that
information and security
rarely gohand-in-hand.
Which is why I have beentold rather late
that someone iskilling our subjects.
Thank you, Tomas.
Why did you letthe imposter live?
She's differentthan the others.
But how could it be different?
I don't know.
We have a connection.
But it's nothing.
Just one of yourfingernail clippings,
like the rest of them.
She said I am not the original,
that we are all the same.
How could you believesuch a thing?
Forgive me, Tomas.
Why are you following me?
I'm not following you.
Fine.
I thought you mightwant a blowjob.
Shit. Shit!
Hey, Paul, Paul.
He's with me, okay?He's my brother.
Jesus Christ, Sarah.
What are you doing here?
Sorry.I was worried.
What happened?
Not here.
Meet me at home.
Don't bring him.
Okay.You all right?
Yeah.
Your task is more difficult,
since the real Beth Childs
shot our friend Maggie Chen.
The copies,
they're harder to find.
Maybe we could usethe imposter.
I'd like to see her again.
Tomas.
It will say anything
to justify itself.
I'll be strong.
The path to the Shepherd
is through the sheep.
Find the impostor,
bleed it for what it knows,
then kill it.
You are the original.
You are the light.
I am the original.
I am the light.
Let's go overwhat you know again.
There's nine of you.
No! There'sonly one of me,
just like there wasone of Beth.
That's not what I meant.
Yeah, Beth figured outthere were nine of us,
so far.
I've only met Alison.
Who else knows,besides your brother?
Just me and Alison.
What about Alison's husband?
They've been togethersince high school.
He's not her monitor.We don't know that.
Don't lie to me, Sarah.
What is going on?
Is Olivier on to us, or what?
Olivier told me someoneis killing the subjects.
You know anything about that?
No.
Who?
He just said to watchBeth closely,
protect her, make sureshe's not aware.
Aware of what?
Of me, of us.
This is high-levelshit, Sarah,
an illegal human-cloning trial.
You think I don't know that?Aren't you the least bit worried
that someone might betrying to kill you?
Yes.
But at least it's not you.
And I still needto see my daughter.
Take my car.
It's in the underground.
Why?
In case someone istailing you, all right?
My job is to keep you safe.
At least let me do that.
Shit!
I'm not here to hurt you.
I just want to talk.
Helena,just stay away from me!
Please. I havean offer for you.
But we must talk.
And eat.
Let's have lunch.
Lunch?
¢Ü They say we're youngand we don't know ¢Ü
¢Ü Won't find out
I dreamed thatwe were friends.
We're not friends.
We will be.
I've seen it.
Don't they feed you,wherever you go?
¢Ü I got you
this is a nicerestaurant, isn't it?
Yeah, five stars.
¢Ü I got you, babe
mm.
You know my name.
Tell me yours.
This friendshipisn't there yet.
You're Russian?
No.
I grew up pure ina convent in Ukraine.
Ukrainian nuns?
Is that who made youkill Katja Obinger
and the others?
No.
¢Ü I got you, babe
they saved mefrom abandonment.
Excuse me.
¢Ü I got you
I want my knife back,
the one you took from me.
Right, right,the flying-fish blade.
You got a thing forwings, don't you?
Mm.
I'm supposed to kill you, too.
But you let me live.
Yeah, so let'scall it even, okay?
We'll go our separate ways.
We'll never be separate.
Tell me the names of the others
and I will spare you.
You move your foot,
or I'll stab you again.
You have until midnight
to tell me the names.
Call this number,
or you die first.
¢Ü I got you
bye-bye.
¢Ü I got you, babe
Beth's paperwork's a mess.
It's like she's never doneit before. Jane Doe's
fingerprint resultsaren't even filed here.
Yeah, I know.We ran 'em. No match.
Yes, Beth checked the results.
I remember, but even ifthere's no match,
they should still be here.
The man said double-check everything,
so let's get forensicsto pull the hand,
run a fresh set of prints.
Oh, we're hitting the morgue?
Thought you'd like that.
Sweet.
Hello.
You havea problem.
What kind of a problem?
I just received the results
of Beth's medical exam.
- Okay.- She's not Beth.
Well, which one is she,if she's not Beth?
That's none of your concern.
Just bring her in.
She's back?
Yeah, and she wantsyour names by midnight,
or I'm first on her hit list.
Holy shit, Sarah.
Don't worry.I won't give you up.
You know, maybe you should.
Not to Helena, but to Olivier.
What?
You were the one who said,if your blind subject
suddenly became aware,you'd terminate.
Right, well,
I'm beginning to rethink that.
Great, she's gota new hypothesis.
So, our creators,
whoever they are, they have
a tremendous investmentin us, right?
Our conception,our whole lives.
Don't you think they'd try
to protect us from Helena?
They know somebody'swhacking us.
Shit.
Yeah, and Paul saidit's more of the same...
Observe your lab rat,
keep her stupid.
Do you know this futurist,
Dr. Aldous Leekie?
- No.- You know, he's the poster boy
for this movementcalled "Neolution".
Eh, Neolution?
Olivier owns a clubcalled Neolution.
Oh, that's interesting.
Yeah, Felix said it'sa bunch of biohack,
bodymod freaks.
Olivier's supposed tohave a tail.
A tail, for real?
Yeah.
That's what Felix was told.
Okay, well, tail or no tail,
they have a philosophy.
I went with Delphine
to one of Leekie'sNeolution lectures.
Cosima, you agreed to stayaway from Delphine.
No, I didn't.You just told me to.
You're going to end upstrapped to a gurney,
with doctors givingyou the probe.
I probably already have been.
Can we please justget back to Helena?
You know what?Just stay out
of my end, I'llstay out of yours.
Bitch.
Shit!
Shit.
Hi.
Hey.
Sorry, I'm...
Oh, I'm early?
- No, no no no, I'm late, I'm late.- Okay.
I'm kind of alwayslate, though,
so, kind of always sorry.
Can you give metwo seconds? Just...
Of course.Okay.
Where is she?
How'd you get in here?
My key.
We bought this placefor you, remember?
So that you wouldnot only appear
attractive to Beth, but,
moderately successful.
Where is your subject?
She's visiting Christine.
You were to keepa close eye on her.
It was a girls' lunch.I couldn't force the issue.
Astrid.
Your subject isn'twho we think she is.
She's an imposter.
I saw her justa few hours ago.
It wasn't her.
Is this a test of some kind?
The person killing our subjects
looks exactly like Beth.
You mean like a twin?
Yes, Paul,
like a twin.
Now, get dressed.
Mom.
Sorry.
Sorry, Monkey.
That was wonderful.That was really good.
Well, at least
she didn't get your tin ear.
I never learned to play piano.
You were too bad, weren't you?
Eh.Your mom just
didn't work hardenough at it, love.
All right, move over.
I want to teach her some queen.
Uncle Felix wasn't bad.
He was a different kind of bad.
What's this?
Mostly me.
But some of you.
Englandwas burning,
Maggie Thatcher
firing on all barrelsat Ireland,
the Falklands.
She sacked Social Security,
went after theimmigrants, the poor,
the unions.
What do you rememberabout Brixton,
about my people, then?
Not much.
There were alwayswomen around.
Kids would come and go,wards of the state.
They weren't all wards.
We were a...
A safehouse.
Some of us workedin Social Services,
helping womenand kids, refugees,
deportees,radicals on the run,
that kind of thing.
And...
This boy, Carlton.
Yeah, Carlton.
I remember him.
He was a fine boy.
Fine man.
Sometimes his pipelinewould bring in
a child in the black,a child to hide.
You were one of them.
Why'd he have to hide me?
We didn't ask what wedidn't need to know.
I had the chance
to legitimize a child,
so I became yourlegal guardian.
The last time I heardfrom Carlton,
he was about to be arrested
and he warned me,
he begged me,to move you away,
to hide you deeper.
So,
I left everyone I knew
and I brought you
and Felix here.
I should've left himwhen I left Paris.
Mm, yeah, cold turkey,
it's the only way to go.
"Cold turkey", what is that?
Oh, it means "abruptly".
Oh, yes, that"what I should've...
You know, he wassupposed to follow
next month, but,
I changed my mind.
Oh, my God.You're the asshole.
Mm-hmm, I am thecold-turkey asshole.
Dr. Leekie!
So nice to see you.
It's Dr. Leekie.
Should we invite him?
Your usual table?
You're single now.
Oh, no no no.He's too old.
But his mind is sexy.
Oui, c'est vrai.
I will go get him.
You know you guysalready checked
- the prints, right?- Oh, yeah.
We're looking at thewhole chain again.
Check that shit out.Finger straightener.
You are in the wrongdepartment, Angie.
You want her?
Ha ha.
Hey, you ever seen
a postmortem spasm?
Well, I'm still tryingto work it out
with my advisors,but my dissertation is
on epigenetic influenceon clone cells.
Oh, it's a fascinating field.
Yeah.
Are either of you familiar
with our workat the Dyad Institute?
Oh, your immunologypapers, yes.
Then you'll be interestedin this too, Delphine...
We've created a pluripotent
stem cell line fromhuman baby teeth.
Dr. Leekie,
you've perfecteda number of proprietary
cloning techniques...in bacteria,
amphibians, insects,human skin grafts.
Correct.
And you're patenting
transgenic embryonicstem cells?
We hope to, once we getthe necessary approvals,
but that is notpublic knowledge.
Yeah, I did some digging,
and then just guessed.
She...she is very, very...
- what's the word?- "Cheeky", I think,
is the word you'reafter, "cheeky".
She is very cheeky, this girl.
But that's why I like her.
Beth's dead?
Why?
I can't tell you that.
Who is she?
All I can tell you is
that she comes from Europe.
So, did this imposterkill Beth?
We suspect so.
And she's killedother subjects.
Yet, Paul, she still seems
to share your bed.
I don't know whatto say, Olivier.
To me, she's still Beth.
Regardless of what you think,
I need you to bring her to me.
Where in Europe?
Does that matter?
Yeah.
It's a big place.
England, Spain, what?
Whether I believe you or not,
loyalty is provenin the moment,
after all.
And loyalty has its rewards.
I know what I did, Olivier.
Help make this right,Afghanistan goes away,
you're free ofyour debt to us.
You get your life back, Paul.
Okay.
Can I have my phone back?
What do you think,the both of you,
of applying to the institute?
Who, us?
Well, why not?
You could be the nextWatson and Crick!
I'm just a geek girlfrom Berkeley.
I can tell you have
a very unique
perspective, Cosima.
Please, you could be
on the cover ofScientific American.
Scientific American
doesn't put scientistson the cover.
Well,
every rule needs to be broken.
Here.
If you... if youhave to go back
to go forward,I understand, but,
just tell me, okay?
It might still be dangerous.
Yeah, I think so, too.
I can keep Kira safe,
just like I kept you.
Put it on speaker.
One more story, mummy?
Ah!
You already hada story, didn't you?
It's time for bed. Oh.
Monkey-swingto Felix.
Okay.Oh, my gosh!
Come on, I'll squeezeyou to sleep.
I'll be right up, okay?
Do your teeth!
Hello?
Hi, Beth.
What's up?
Not much.
I need you to dosomething for me.
Okay.
They know you're not Beth.
Run.
Okay, I get it, I do.
Black-ops Pauljust proved
he's down with you for real,
but he also said run.
I can't just leavehim in there, Fe.
It's probably my fault
he's in there,in the first place.
Well, how do you evenknow he's still here?
I don't, but I've got to try.
So, then, what areyou going to do?
Are you going to takeCosima's bad advice,
fess up to Olivier?
I've got an even worse idea.
How was your day, Paul?
Yes, I also had a pleasant day.
I went working and shopping.
Pardon me.It's work.
It's almost midnight.
Do you have names for me?
I do.
Olivier.
That's not the name
of a sheep.
A sheep?
Baa!
Look, Helena,
he's more importantthan a sheep, okay?
He's a Shepherd.
I need you to come meet me.
I saw Paul come upfrom the basement.
I know that Olivier's office
has got to be down there.
Okay, if I'm not backin 15 minutes,
call Art,
tell him everything,
and make sureKira's safe, yeah?
Yeah, I...
Sarah!
What?
Um,
just don't die,
because your first funeral
was just agonizing enough.
What are you doing
down here?
I'm looking for Olivier.
Who are you?
You know how bad this can get.
I'm not working for anyone.
Then why protect her?
I told you she was a killer.
Was she that good?
I have Beth
to see you.
You must be Olivier.
Well,
this is unexpected.
She was carrying this.
I told you to run.
Yeah, I don't do run.
Leave us, please.
Call me as soon as you can.
All these years,I've never seen
one of you in the flesh.
You're even morebeautiful in person.
He thinks you're the killer.
Me?
You've got it all wrong.
We have medical evidence
that proves you're not Beth.
How can you tell that,
if we're genetically identical?
I'm not a scientist.
Well, you've still gotthe wrong girl.
The one who's killingus is blonde,
she's Ukrainian,she's a religious nut.
You've createda whole new brand
of fratricide.
You're not listening.It's not me.
Exquisite.
What do you people want?
The future.
Self-directedevolution?
You want to grow a tail,
that's your business.
Oh, you know aboutmy modest enhancement?
You've got a tail?
The fact thatI can have a tail,
millions of yearsafter we shed it,
reminds me ofwhat we can achieve.
Would you like to see it?
God, no.
Argentinean biohack.
Blood flow, nerve endings,
warm to the touch.
But it's merelyperformance art,
compared to you.
You are our greatestachievement.
Perhaps later.
This is Olivier.
What's so urgent?
I have her, Aldous.
The killer.
Get her ready to travel.
I'll be there in the morning.
And be careful with her.
She's irresistible,
isn't she?
Now I know why you did this.
If I was in your position,
I'd fall in lovewith her, too.
Shh, shh shh shh shh.
Hello, friend.
Oh, God!About time.
Do you want to be saved?
Yes, Helena!Untie me.
Give me a name, first.
I gave you Olivier.
I want the nameof a sheep, too.
Okay, I'll give youanother name.
Tell me.
I offered you a way out,
and you made a fool of me.
You made afatal error, Paul...
You trustedthe wrong person.
Who are you?
I want to see your tail.
Now, show me the tail.
Slowly.
That's good.
Ahh.
How is this possible?
Did you liewith a beast?
Please.You're a miracle.
Let me help you.
I have a messagefor your master.
From Tomas.
Aaaaah!
Aaaaaaaaaaah!
I guess there's a few thingsI should've told you.
You think?
Come on, Sarah.
Yeah, one sec.
Detective Art Bell.
Hi, um, detective.
You don't know me, but, um,
I need to talk to youabout Beth Childs.
Beth Childs?What about her?
I was told to call, um...
Shit! Christ!
Let's go.
Wrong number.
Hello?
Hello!
You had to giveHelena a name?
Yeah, mine.
I told her who I was.
Sarah?
She's got a thing for me.
Mm.
Well, three's a crowd,
so I'm going to go get drunk
by myself at Bobby's Bar.
We can't go backto the townhouse.
It's not safe. They'llbe looking for us.
We should...
Working withDr. Leekie could be
the opportunity of a lifetime.
I know.
Then why are youbeing so coy?
Don't you think
it's time we admit what this is
really about?
I, um...
Oh. Oh, God,Delphine.
Uh... did I makea huge mistake?
No.
I have to go.
It-it's okay.
Bye.
Delphine, just...
Hey, I'm going home.
You should, too.
Ha ha. What, and missall the fun?
Art!
Art, you got to see this.
Holy shit.
It's a matchon the Jane Doe print.
Who's Sarah Manning?
And why the hell doesshe look like Beth?
Siobhan Sadler?
Who wants to know?
Detectives Bell and DeAngelis.
Get out of the car, Alison!
You have
no idea
who you're dealing with!
Where are you with Cosima?
I can't stop thinkingabout that kiss.
- Welcome to the big picture.- Yes, sir.
Siobhan, this is
Alison Hendrix.