The German was sick. ShouldI be worried about that?
Art... you're aboutthe only person I trust
to figure the whole thing out.
You need a warrantfor Sarah Manning.
They can tell usapart by our DNA.
Dig faster.
Cosima's safety is at stake.
Well, she'snot only researching
her own biology,
but she is awareof eight others.
You know, I've never beenwith a woman before.
Yeah, it showed.
Maybe it's not just Aynsley.Maybe they're all monitors.
You want to mess with my life?I'm going to mess with yours.
I'm about to giveHelena to Leekie.
Sorry. She saidshe'd be here.
I grew up pure ina convent in Ukraine.
No!
Where's Helena? I tiedher up in the trunk.
Sarah!
Sarah, this is Amelia.
I'm your birth mother.
I had twins.One to the state
and one to the church.
Helena.
Ready?
Yes.
I carried you both.I need to see her.
I don't think that ninemonths of gestation
entitles her to risk us all.
Hey, look, Helena'smy twin sister.
She has a right to know.
Because you shared a womb?
Helena.Is. Dangerous.
She's had her whole worldturned inside out,
just like I have.
How Helena takes this
determines what we do with her.
I need to see you privately,
away from here.
What for?
I have something for you.
From back then,
about my in vitro treatments.
Okay, I've got a place
we can meet.
Helena,
this is Amelia, your birth mum.
Eh, look. Hey!
You listen to whatshe has to say,
or I'll put you rightback in the trunk
and I'll take youstraight to Leekie.
How can you be my birth mother?
Helena,
I am birth mother to you both.
Who's here?
Ah... monkey, you're notsupposed to be up!
What's the matter, love?
I think something bad
is going to happen again.
Yeah, that's what this is,
our connection.
We were implanted by doctors,
all of us.
You split inside me,into two baby girls
and I hid you because
I felt you were in danger.
Sestra.
You're my twin sister.
I don't want to beyour sister, meathead.
Look, I just want you to know
you're not the original.
Got it? You were bornof science,
not of some immaculate womb,
or whatever bullshitTomas fed you.
This is the police!
- Shit. Sarah!- We have a warrant!
This isyour last warning!
Sit down.You're just visiting.
Sarah Manning!
- Come out with your hands up!- Come out now!
Put your hands on your head!
- Turn around!- Hands up, now!
Sarah Manning,you're under arrest.
Let's go.
Orphan Black 01x10Endless Forms Most Beautiful
Original Air Date June 1, 2013
Sarah.
I still see Beth.
I didn't kill her, Art.
No.
You watched her commit suicide
and then you wentstraight for her wallet.
Beckwith finished
Jane Doe's facialreconstruction.
Who's this one?
You've been obstructingthis investigation
from the minute youtook over Beth's life.
You're the primesuspect, Sarah.
I didn't kill her, Art!
You know who did?
We've got yourfoster brother Felix
in custody for abettingand your daughter?
She's going to beone lonely little girl,
unless you start talking!
You wouldn't believe it.
Yeah?
Try me.
Good, slide it out again, go.
Go, come on,feel it work. Go.
Mnh! Push it up.
You got it.Clap it high.
You know what?
Slide it out for 2.Here's 2.
Slide it to the rightagain. Go...
Mnh!
Yeah?
Alison!
Dr. Aldous Leekie.
It's a lovely home.
I'm warning you...
I'm armed.
What do you want?
To make amends.
So, you want meto sign a contract.
No, more like a treaty...
Rules both sides will abide by.
Even though everythingyou've done is illegal.
You must think I'm so stupid.
Stupid, suburban Alison.
Quite the opposite.
You're a pragmaticand decisive individual
and, now thatyou're self-aware,
we can start to answersome of your questions.
I don't wantanswers anymore.
I want my life back.
I want my family back,I want my privacy back,
I want you out of my life!
And I want thingsto be normal again.
I'm so glad you said so.
This enshrines yourfamily's freedom,
guarantees protection
from the likes of Helena,
and ensures you'll beunmonitored.
Unmonitored?
Yes.
But in return, you agree
to twice-yearlymedical testing,
private and noninvasive.
I don't want to scare you, but,
there are health concerns...
Katja's respiratory disorder,
Helena's mental illness.
Regular testing is
in everyone's best interest.
So,
read it over,
discuss it withSarah and Cosima.
And, as a gestureof good faith,
your monitor has been lifted.
She has?
Mm-hmm.
Don't get up.
You purposely misidentified
the body of a police officer.
It was a terrible caseof mistaken identity.
You know it's fraud byfalse representation.
That's 2 to 5,with your priors.
I thought it was my sister.
You know,
Angela Deangelis,
I'm actually quite a fan.
Hmm.
But you really needto get laid.
Yeah, tell me about it.
But all I seem to meetare gay men.
So,
public defender, then, is it?
We'll get youa real shitty one.
Thank you.
Cosima!
Please,
don't be alarmed.
I'm beyond alarmed.I'm pissed.
Let me give you a liftto your hotel.
I have an offer youmay find interesting.
It's your phone.
Well, it's Beth'sphone, actually.
So help me wrap my head
around this.
Art, if you're hearing this,
you found the body.
It's not Beth.It's me.
My name is Sarah Manning and...
You're about the onlyperson I trust
to figure the whole thing out.
Sarah, my partnerkilled herself.
I didn't see it coming.
Help me.
Help Beth.
I know you care.
There's a reason
we look exactly the same, Art.
Okay.
Why the prints match,
and the DNA's all screwed up.
But you have to promise
to protect me and my daughter.
I will.
If that's what you need,
I promise.
Detective, thisinterview is over.
What is this?
Sorry, Art.
Miss Manning, I'm your lawyer,
Daniel Rosen.
Unshackle her, please.
Miss Manning will beleaving with me.
Thank you, gentlemen.Miss Manning.
This is an employment contract
for the Dyad Institute.
Very generous compensation.
We want to workwith you, Cosima.
You'vegot to be kidding me.
This is your completesequenced genome.
3.2 billionbase pairs.
My offer
is the freedomto study yourself
and your sisters.
Unfettered research.
We share the same concerns,
the same questions aboutorganism stability,
but nobody... nobody...
Is more invested in yourown biology than you!
It's yours.
Just think about it.
Where are you taking me?
We had your brotherreleased as well.
Who's "we"? You workfor Dr. Leekie?
Indirectly.
Great, should've known.
Can we have a minute?
You left me hangingwith Leekie
when you didn'tshow up with Helena.
Do you work for Leekie now?
They still haveAfghanistan on me,
understand?
What is that?
You changed the gamefor everyone, Sarah.
Now, I can onlyhelp you from here.
Listen to whatthey have to say.
Do I have a choice?
Right.
Sarah Manning.
So,
my name is Rachel Duncan
and we are going tocome to terms.
The agreement defines
mutual disclosureand formalizes contact
with what I call "Top Side".
"Top Side"?
So is this the partwhere 20 more
of you robot bitcheswalk in for effect?
You're not an orphananymore, Sarah.
We found you
and my role isto transition you
to self-awareness.
A clone fixer.
Brilliant.
You know,
maybe it's time I justembraced my clonage,
went on "Oprah".
We could be famous,you and me.
We're not the enemy.
Helena and her ilk are
and we are going tohelp with that.
You want to help?
Why don't you tell me why?
What am I doing, sathere, looking at you?
What are we for?
Disclosure
is defined herein.
We want your trust.
You want precious answers
that cut to the coreof who you are.
But, above all,
I know you want to makethe right choice
for Kira.
You're very lucky.
Motherhood is wonderful.
The forces behind Helena
will never stop, Sarah.
The most importantthing in this for you
is protection
for you and your daughter.
Yeah, no, thanks.
I'll get by on my own.
Scrambling to stay alive?
You'll remain free
to live as you wish with Kira,
provided for;
unmonitored, but available.
Call it "sovereigntyassociation."
Yeah, like I said,
I'm not interested.
Take 24 hours
to think about it.
Midnight tomorrow.
They're offering ussecurity, a truce.
Rachel didn't feellike a truce.
She felt likea gun to the head.
Okay, little reminder?
While you and Iwere being arrested,
Helena escaped.
Yeah, thank you, Fe.
Would you also liketo remind me
my birth mum popped round
and Helena's my twin sister?
Ah, Jesus Murphy.
Hey.
Hi.
Uh, Sarah, I
so should've listened to you
about Delphine.I...
You're all right.
A career at the Dyad Institute.
Yeah, studying us.
What are yougoing to do, Cosima?
Well,
we have to knowour own biology.
That's what thisis all about, right?
Maybe I can help us best
from the inside.
I want to know whatyou're going to do.
Well, I can't trust thisRachel bitch, can I?
Not if Kira's the firstchild of a clone,
scientifically unclassified.
She could be whatRachel's actually after.
Who is Rachel?Can someone tell me?
So she doesn't justshow up at my door
and I have no idea who she is.
Amelia said
she heard her doctors,back in the day,
discussing a childraised by neolution.
She's a proclone?
God, you threeare weird enough.
Well, if there won't beany more spies
in my life,if my kids are safe,
I'm sorry,
but I have to tell youI'm inclined
to take the offer.
Yeah, that's okay.
That's totally your choice.
Yeah, no judgment.
Oh, shit.
Delphine just got off a plane.
Here? Stupid,needy bitch.
Right.
She wants to help, right?
Just like Art, Paul,and Rachel.
Everybody wants to help.
I'm going to Mrs S's.
I want to be therewhen Kira wakes up.
I'll catch up.
Yeah, I mean, we makeour own decisions,
but I wouldn't trust anybody.
Katja Obinger.
German?
Yeah.
We finally ID'ed our Jane Doe
and she falls underFederal jurisdiction.
This whole thing reeks.
Hey, you still wantto get to the bottom
of Sarah Manning?
I found a known associate.
I guess my turning point was
when the love of my life...
Let's just call her "Sarah"...
Sarah broke up with meby faking her own death,
initiating events which began
with the loss of my finger,
led to variousother humiliations,
and, ultimately,
to the business endof a nail gun.
That's when I justsaid to myself
"I need help.I need help."
So
Like I said before,my name's Victor.
I'm an addict,maybe, you know, so...
Peace out.
You're moving.
Yes. Chad got his ownplace with the dog
and I got a very handsome offer
on the house.
It's the perfect opportunity
to get the kids out ofthis toxic environment.
Mm, that's priceless.
Goodbye, Alison.I'm packing.
Oh, Alison, get out!
Admit it!
Admit what?!
That I organizedyour intervention?
My bad.Sorry I care.
Dr. Leekie cameto see me.
Who?
Cray-cray! If it'sprofessional help,
I'm all for it.
I want the truth, Aynsley!
- The truth?!- Mm-hmm.
Is that you screwed my husband
and I'm moving because of you!
Look at this!Yours!
Gifts from my best friend!
A felt Christmas angel.
I made that!
- Yeah?- Yes!
Well, to hell with you
and your Christmas angel.
You know, you,
you turned this wholething around on me
because you're jealous.
You're barrenand you can't have
your own children!
Oh!
Oh.
Oh, my God!
Alison, help!
Uggh!
Ohh!
Alison, help me!
Ow!
Ahh!Alison!
Alison!
Aynsley.
Aynsley?
Nice speech.
Yeah, I'm moved, personally.
Isn't this place off-limits to you guys?
You know, sacredground or something?
Not if you gotan outstanding warrant
for selling stolen meat?
No, smoked pork.
I didn't know it was stolen.
You know, that's lame,
but I'll take the collar.
Eh, c'mon, c'mon, c'mon, man!
I'm trying to turnmy life around.
All right, okay, so thengive us something useful
on your femme fataleSarah Manning.
Of course, Sarah.
Step 9 of the program,
I got to suck it upand apologize
for shit that I did to her.You believe that?
But, since she's not going toapologize back...
Last time I saw Sarah,she was playing housewife
in the suburbs.
Husband, kids, minivan,the whole shebang.
That...
That isn't SarahManning, is it?
No.
That is anotherperson, entirely.
You got to befriggin' kidding me.
When police come,mummy goes away.
No, darling, not this time.
She's back.
To keep us safe from Helena.
Don't worry about Helena,
Kira, okay?
I don't.
She's not a real monster.
Okay,
we're going tohave to hide this bag.
We might have to go on a trip,
but you can't tell anybody.
Eh.
Not even Mrs S.
It's a secret.
Yeah? Promise?
Okay.
Do you have a spare toothbrush?
Go get it.
- Go.- Okay.
Where are you off to?
Meeting Amelia.
You all right?
Just edgy, withHelena in the wind.
Yeah.
Sarah, mind Amelia.
Why?
It's true, right, thatshe's my birth mum?
Yeah, it all seemsto track, just...
She didn't raise you.
Yeah, I know.
You did.
It was all a long time ago.
You all right?
Yeah.Yeah, sorry.
Oh.
Well, now, I get it.
Um, is Cosima...?is sh...
It's Delphine!
She's got baggage!
You know, if Sarah were here,
she'd kick your willowy arse.
I promise you...
I did not tell Leekieabout Sarah's child.
What difference does it make?
Why are you here?
Because I...
Because Leekie is a liar
and I think you canprove it scientifically
with that, yoursynthetic sequence.
He gave me my whole genome.
But you can't find
that sequence anymore, can you?
He would've scrubbed it.
Don't.
I'm on your side now.
Please believe me.
You need to trust someone.
I think the sequence is
a message.
Like
Dr. Craig Venter
watermarked his synthetic DNA.
It's a key to our origins.
May I?
Mm-hmm.
Okay.
Thank you formeeting me, Sarah.
Drink?
Just water.
That poor child, Helena.
How can two fates beso different?
You two are likenight and day.
Thank you.
I'm sorry to bring yousuch burdens,
but I must warn you, Sarah.
Your foster mother, Mrs S,
she's not who she says she is.
I have somethingyou should see.
How did scientists
put babies inside you?
What?
You gave me to them.
You let them make me this way.
No!
Oh!
Helena,what have you done?
We missed you, sister.Come join us.
Alison?
Donnie...
Ally.
Ally, you're shaking.
I'm a horrible person.
No. No, honey.I am.
I let those people in our home.
They had no right
to intervention you like that.
They don't know the real you.
Oh, Judas priest.What have I done?!
No, no, no no no.
It doesn't matter.
We can put it all behind us,
every little bit of it. Really?
Yeah.
Really?!
Okay, here's thesynthetic sequence.
And this is thedifferentiated portion.
Yes, this isan encrypted I.D. tag.
It's how they tell you apart.
Okay. But howto decode it?
I have four nucleotidesto work with...
G, C, T, and A...
And no idea how they'reencrypted. I mean,
there's thousandsof permutations
and we're running out of time.
Yes, but I knowyour tag number.
You do?
Yes, I saw it many times.
It's numeric, so,
if we know how that translates,
then we can figureout the rest.
Okay.What is it?
It's 324b21.
324b21.
Right.
I'm 324b21.
I'm sorry.
Well, let's run these letters
through a decryption program.
Yeah.
Helena!
Ugh! Noneof these results
match the I.D. tag.
Okay.Okay, think.
We're molecular-encoding,
from 30 years ago.
Yes, but we're lookingat it from now.
Of course.
They weren'tcoding nucleotides.
It was whole base pairs?
Not four letters,but two, AT and GC.
Ones and zeros.
Binary.
They were coding in ASCII!
Shit!
Amelia!
Amelia.
Amelia...
Keep pressure.
I'm going to get you help.
What's this?
Your foster mother.
She what?She what?
Foster mother.
Shh shh shh.
She What?
Moja Sestra.
My twin.
Amelia.
I'm sorry, motherisn't very well.
She's dead,
you psycho.
You killed someone I'vebeen dreaming about
my whole life.
She separated us.
She tore us apart.
But,
now, we're together.
No, we're not.
You're nothing to me,
just some crazy bitch
wearingmy t-shirt.
"London Calling".
Scientists made one little baby
and then we split in two.
So I cannot kill you,
sister.
Like you could not kill me.
Sarah.
We make a family, yes?
I've already got a family.
Okay,moment of truth.
324b21.
It's your I.D. tag.You cracked it.
Let's see what else there is.
Okay,
CAGT...
GT...
Rachel Duncan.
It's Sarah.
Yes, Sarah?
I wantto know my daughter
won't have to live like this.
We can do that.
I'm coming in.
One down, two to go.
What's going on over there?
Oh!
None of our business.
Your tracksuit!
Mm-hmm.
I'm going for a jog.
I've been a lump.You deserve better.
Hmm.
I feel like a weighthas been lifted.
- All right.- Okay.
- Here we go.- Bye. Have fun.
- See you in a bit.- Be safe.
I will.
Going up.
Sarah.
Don't!
You asked me
what happened in Afghanistan.
I was a private contractor.
I killed six marines.
Friendly fire.
They covered it up.
That's what they have on me.
If you were bornoutside their control,
what do theyreally have on you?
Yeah?
Sarah,you can't make a deal.
Why not?
Any freedom they promiseis bullshit.
They're liars.
That synthetic sequence,
the barcode I told you about?
It's a patent.
A patent?
We're property.
Our bodies, our biology,
everything we are,everything we become,
belongs to them.
Sarah, they could claim Kira.
They patented us.
Back on track, I think.
It's the7-year itch.
It's not easy.
She's not easy.
_
You know what to do.
"This organism
and derivative genetic material
is restrictedintellectual property".
I'm sick, Delphine.
Siobhan!
Kira!
Kira-a-a!