I saw a girl kill herself.
And she looked exactly like me.
Elizabeth Childs.
I'm going to go up to her flat.
To find out who she is or torob the rest of her shit?
Hello?
Holy shite.
Beth is a cop. I'm a cop.
Is this evil twin's money?
Yeah, that's enough to getsomewhere safe with my daughter.
I'm going to hang on to thatmoney until you're cleared.
Who the hell is Maggie chen?
That's the woman Beth shot.
- Beth. What's happened?- A lot.
Something's different.You are not Beth.
The German's dead.
Someone shot herright in front of me!
Holy shit, it's true! What?
That someone is killing us.
Beth, you need toget rid of the body.
Did you get theGerman's briefcase?
No. Why?
Get the briefcasebefore they do.
- Screw it.- Hello?
Who is this?
Beth's indisposed.Is this Alison?
How dare you show your facein front of my children.
This is my neighborhood.
You wait for a call.
Hey.
I'm Cosima.
How many of us are there?
Okay, define "orphan", Sarah.
Orphan, orphanage.
So, you don't knowyour birth parents?
No, I was fostered out,
then legally adoptedand I came here.
When?
Adopted? Like 8.Came here around 12.
Heartbreaking. Can we getback to Beth, please?
Suicide?
I don't accept that.
This one's some kind oflowlife grifter!
How do we knowshe didn't push her?
Oi! I already told you...I didn't want to be her.
I got stuck! I was runningfrom my own shit.
I can only imagine.
Alison, I'm very sorryabout Beth, okay?
But she was losing it,
like, clinically.
She was a cop. She had tools.
If she couldn't cope,then, I mean...!
Look, can you just tell me
what the hell this is?
Don't tell her anything!
- Short answer?- No.
How are we all related?
We're not!
Well, we are, by nature.
She's referring to nurture.
Just give us the briefcasethat you got from the German.
I'm not giving you shit 'tilyou give me some answers.
You don't rate answers.
Alison!
Fine! She wants in?We're clones.
We're someone's experimentand they're killing us off!
Is that helpful?!
Hmm?
Mommy?
Gemma!
Who are those ladies?
Da da da da da.Just mommy's friends.
How did you get out of bed?
Sorry.
I wanted to float
that whole clone thinga lot softer.
Come on, Sarah.
Shite!
You're not supposed to beparked here at night.
I'm waiting for someone.
Well, this isa neighborhood watch
block, so...
Come on, girl.
Bitch that guards hell.
Screw it.
We are geneticallyidentical, or whatever.
It's actually kind of cool.
As far as...
shit! Shit!
Su...
was there someone there?
Oh, my God!
Freeze! What are youdoing in my yard?
Don't! Do not shoot me! Please!
Why are you here?! Do not shoot!Please!
Hey! Alison! Alison!Put it down.
Get out of the way!
He's with me! Okay?
Move!
It's okay.
Oh, shit!
You point a gunat my brother again,
I will kick the livingshite out of you!
We need to get my shit.
What the hellwere you doing here?
Hey, you need this?
You just broke the firstrule of clone club.
What, "never tell anyoneabout clone club"?
Hi.
Awkward. I'm Cosima.
You have my number.
You want answers?I want the briefcase.
Seriously, it's life-or-death.
You've got to be kidding me.
Clones?
Clones?!
They're not me. They're not.
They're completelydifferent people.
Soccer-mum Sarah,
dreadlock science-geek Sarah?
Arguably more attractivethan the real Sarah.
Yeah, I was there, thank you.
How can it be, though?
What difference doesit make, Fe?
Last time I checked,human cloning
was illegal,let alone impossible.
Yeah, leave it out, okay?It doesn't matter!
It does matter!
Dead Beth, dead German,those two,
three other Euros,you... that's eight.
And dreadlocks is going onabout her blood samples,
saying it's life-or-death.You can't just ignore it.
Yes, I can!
I'm just me, okay?
The song remains the same.
We get the 75 grand backfrom Beth's partner,
we get Kira,and get as far away
from all this as possible!
Am I going insane?
Hey, Beth.
I thought you were still off.
Uh, yeah, justcan't get enough.
Is Art around?
Beth! What the hell's going on?
Yeah, I got to talk to you
for a couple seconds.
Hey, company?
Yeah.
Look, things are bad with Paul.
Okay.
We're dividing upour shit. Any second,
he's going to find thatjoint account empty.
Look, you get the cashwhen you're back
on active duty.That's the deal.
Childs!
Sorry, just saying hello.
No, you're not. Both of you.
Bad news...
you're reinstated.
Oh, shit!
Welcome back.
Well, thank God.
Buckle up, kid,
we got a 10-45.
Uh, hey,
two seconds.
Shit.
Do you want help with that?
Yeah, you mind?
Quarry road and ulster.
Confirmed 10-45.Forensic onsite.
So, Art, about our deal.I'm reinstated now.
Hey, I'm not carrying around
75 grand in the trunk,all right?
Just call us in.
- Heading for the 10-45.- Roger.
Responder, please identify.
Uh...
Fifty-five.
Fifty-five headingfor the 10-45, Roger.
Out.
Copy.
Ahem! What?
Something wrong?
Body's chewed up pretty bad.
What do you think?
I think some idiotdidn't realize
they were burying a body
next to an active quarry.
Got a pretty goodtire print over there.
I'd say the bodywasn't in the ground
more than two,maybe three, days.
Hey, welcome back.
Now, this would be
your industrial sausagemaker.
Nice of them to lenda hand, though.
Prints?
They'd better hit, because
reconstructing the faceis going to be tough.
Hey!
Can we get the guyto open this thing up?
Uh, I need to makea call, yeah?
One sec.
I can't talk, or meet.Just answer the question.
Oh, okay, okay.
Our fingerprintsare close enough
to flag a match, yeah.
Why?
Beth's partner foundthe German...
or at least part of her.
Part of her?
Yeah, I messed upwhen I buried her.
They have afingerprint, Cosima.
Oh, wait, are youbeing Beth right now?
Pretending to be a bloodycop, so I need to know
if the bloody fingerprints
will flag a bloody match!
Whoa! Okay, okay,don't freak out!
They'd need to use interpol
to find the German,which is unlikely,
but if one of us hada criminal record here...
do you have a criminal record?
Just petty fraud,assault, whatever.
Wasted youth, all right?
If the body matches me,the cops will see
a mugshot of somebody
who looks like Beth,only it's yours truly,
and I'm alreadysupposed to be dead.
Wow. Wow, welcometo the trip, man.
That is not helpful.
Yeah, okay, sorry.Just don't bolt, okay?
Don't bolt.
They can't run printsinstantaneously,
so we do have some time here.
How much time?
Bring me the briefcaseand we'll talk, okay?
Beckwith will have an exacttime of death soon,
but 'til then, I saywe ballpark two,
three days, see who's missing.
And fingerprints,
what, a couple days?
Yeah, you know the lab.Hopefully, overnight.
Look, Art, um,this shit with Paul
is about to go sideways, okay?
I need to get to the bank.
Let me see your weapon.
Huh?
Come on, show it to me.
It's empty.
Yeah, what? We left in a hurry.
You rode with me empty!
Art, it's a 10-45for legs, right, Art,
like, I mean, who am Igoing to shoot?
That's bullshit, Beth,for regs and your partner.
Look, if the shooting has you
trigger-shy, Beth, you got to... no.I'm not, I'm not.
I'm not. Just give mean hour or two
to get up to speed,for Christ's sake.
You can get up to speedon the desk, then.
I'll work this with deangelis.
- Now get outta here.- Hey, Art.
Look, if you ask meabout that money
one more time, Beth,I swear to God,
it's going in the shredder.
Hey.
Don't worry,you get used to it.
To clones?
Yeah, I'm not buying that.
How many of us
do you have to meet, Sarah?
Can I have thebriefcase, please?
I want some answers, first.
Well, the answers arein the briefcase.
Let me guess...
you're the smart one,you're the wild one.
Would you believe we're clones?
Bourbon, rocks.
You got it.
So you're the scientistthe German was on about.
Yes... well, phd student,
evolutionarydevelopmental biology
at university of Minnesota.
I'm heading back there tonight.
The German was sick.
Should I be worried about that?
Well, if you give me the case,
I'll know in a couple weeks.
Do you know whoshot her in the head?
Okay, ahem! So, six months ago,
katja contacted Bethwith this crazy story
about her genetic identicals
being hunted in Europe.
"Hunted"?
Brilliant.
I know.
So Beth used facial-recognition software
to find driver's licenses
in north America.
Two matches.
You and soccer bitch.
Yeah, right.
But who is the original?
Who's created us?
Who's killing us?
We need to know, but,we lost our cop, so,
however you manageto get into her shoes,
we really need youto stay there.
Stay a cop to help you?
To help us.
Help us find outwho's killing us.
How?! I'm not a cop.
Beth's partner'sgoing to figure that out.
Being Beth is whatgot me into this mess,
in the first place.
I know, I know.I get it, I get it.
But you can't runaway from her.
Look, we are yourbiological imperative
now, okay?
Katja's fingerprints
will match your fingerprints.
So get to katja's
fingerprint results, somehow.
I think that's our only option.
All right.
Just answer me one thing...
anything, yes.
If we're genetically identical,
do you get that littlepatch of dry skin
between your eyebrows?
That's good.
Try to keep yoursense of humor.
Beth couldn't.
No cream?
You're booked on the range
day after tomorrow, 4:00.
"The range"?
The gun range?Are you with me or not?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So what about Jane Doe?
Beckwith filled a bucket
with fragments from the hopper.
Couple solids so far...
- dyed red hair.- Like bright red.
And laying outthe skull fragments,
she's 99% sure she foundentry and exit wounds.
A shooting. So whatabout the prints?
Start calling.
And keep callingwhile you clear
that shitpile of a desk.
Hey,
sorry about poachingyour seat on this, eh?
He's all yours.
Let's go. Yeah.
Detective Bell.
Yeah, well, what can youtell me about her?
Jane Doe.
Hey, hey!
Shh! Shh!
You want to give me that again?
Am I speaking
to your partner now, too, Art?
Actually, we lovevoicechange apps,
so the whole officeis listening.
She was just one of a few,
unfit for family, horse glue.
So you didn'tlike her very much.
How about you tell us her name.
She expired at allenside park.
So, what,
Stephen Hawking did it?
The call came to me.
"Just one of a few,unfit for family..."
"Horse glue"? Shit!
What... what else did they say?
They asked if I was thelead on the quarry body.
Listen, before we go,
we'll check the desk,to see who took the call.
Yeah.
Are you going to allenside?
Yeah. Check the log,to see if there were
any shots fired down there.
Hey, look, I'll see youin a bit, okay?
Hey!
Raj.
Detective.
Beth.
Hi.
So you probably knowI've been off
for a while.
Yeah.
Yeah, nightmare.
PTSD, fatal civilian shooting,
inquiry, medication,the whole enchilada.
Gum?
Uh, thanks.
So I guess
you're back, then, right?
Mm, I'm benched.
I'm trying to slip inwithout, you know,
a ripple, but,
on the down-low, I'ma little scattered,
memorywise.
You think you couldhelp with a few basics?
Oh, like resettingyour password?
Yes, like that.
And the whole procedurefor fingerprint results.
I said an hour, Childs.I haven't checked yet.
They're in, though?Because I got
a Jane Doe with zero leads.
They're probably inmy inbox. Just hang on.
Yep, not a problem.
Childs!
"Results from central".I'm helping you out.
I got to log those!
It's all good! Nothing, anyway.
Don't do that again, Childs.
I don't know, Art, you thinksomeone's jerking your chain?
Auto glass.
Hmm.
Looks like a fastexit that way.
I don't see any casings.
Could be line-of-fire,at range.
Hmm.
I've seen your elaborate ruses
and guises before,
but how do you do this,
how do you fake your owndemise beneath a train?
Wouldn't you rather know why?
I don't care to know why.
Because I saw a way to dump Vic
and get out of that life
and get away with Kira.
Ha! Take heron the run with you?
Brilliant.
New clothes and a Jaguardo not a mother make.
Lee of the point.
Ugh! I don't remember.
Buffleheads.
Barrow's goldeneye.Just passing through.
I'll set up a visit,
but the only way
you will regaincustody of Kira is
to show me thatyou can be still.
You're not her legal guardian.
Mine either, anymore.
You can visit.Any other approach,
and I will stop lying tosocial services for you.
You wouldn't do that to Kira.
No.
I'd do it to you.
Hey, someone cleared this out,
laid down in here.
Around here? Probably homeless.
Yeah, but someone movedthis into position.
Hey, this look likea blind to you,
a log for someone
to lay a rifle on?
Weeds knocked downfor sight lines.
Where are you?
Uh, back at school.
What, school?
What? Oh, shit! Right.
Right, right, right.Minneapolis, shit!
What's going on?
Well, I managed to scrapthe fingerprint
results...for a while, anyway...
but the killercontacted Art, Cosima.
He's already at the scene
where katja was shot.
Okay, that's good.Just stick with him.
I can't!
He's benched me becauseI'm bloody useless!
I need help, Cosima.
He wants meon the range tomorrow.
I've never even fired a gun.
All right, well,just hold tight.
We know somebodywho can help with that.
Are you serious?
If you are.
You know we gota motorcycle tread
- over here, Art.- Yeah?
Yeah. Yeah, it's a good print.
Could be the shooter's getaway.
Yeah, but a long gunon a motorcycle?
Could be the weaponbroke down, right?
Yeah, it could be.
Hey, I got something over here.
Head shot.
Bright red hair.
It has to be this morning.
Art's got me chasingdown motorcycle models
from tire tracks and I'mshooting bloody targets
at a gun range tomorrow.
Well, I can't just conjurea sitter out of thin air.
It's weekend primetime, Sarah.
Well, then,
we're all screwed. Aren't we?
Donnie! Ahem.
Can you watch the kids
for a couple of hours today?
Golf. Give it!
On television?
No, I have a tee time,remember?
I'm sorry, I'm coming up empty.
I may have a solution.
Gemma, Oscar, this is Felix.
Hello!
Brilliant.
So I'm going outfor a couple of hours,
so you be good
or mommy's going to bevery upset, okay?
Same goes for you.
So,
what now?
Does your daddy havea drinks trolley?
What's that?
Don't worry. I'll find it.
You.
You want to dress uplike a little girl?
No!
Well, I don't haveanything for you, then.
I'll dress up like a boy.
We can work with that.
No, the make and model
match the treadthat deangelis sent you.
Sports bike, suzuki sv650.
Black tank, custom pipes,
and stolen when?
Reported four days ago.
I should probably get backto my real job now.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.Just, um,
put out a... You know.
An apb.
Yes. Yes, asap.
Sorry, I'm at the the doctor.
My phone's about to die.
Okay, I'll getsomeone to do it.
Thanks, raj.
Well, go.
Okay, reload,
try again.
So, most city copscarry Glocks,
but a walther p99,
it has an optional-sized hand grip.
It's good for women, Beth said,
particularly women
living their liveslike rats in a lab.
Is that what you think?
Well, what else could it be?
Someone is covering uptheir illegal experiments
by wiping us out.
Well, whatever it is,
I need to protect my family,
so Beth taught me how to shoot.
For that, I am grateful to her.
I'm sorry you lost her,
but anything
you can tell meabout her will help.
I fail to see
how someone like youcan fill Beth's shoes.
Truth is, I barely knew Beth.
She was all business,but I admired her.
She didn't pry.
She was discreet.She didn't bring
her foster brother to my house.
I didn't know the rulesof clone club, did I?
Can you not use the c-word?
Please.
Shit.
Stop here. I'll walk the rest.
So my bottom line
is my children can't know
their mother is a freak.
Things have to stayon a need-to-know basis.
Yeah, I'm fine with that.
Good.
So,
we've made a decisionto trust you.
Really?
Sarah, this is my life now
and I'm doing the best I can.
Ahem, so Beth had, um,a substantial sum,
sort of a fund she used to buy
information we couldn'tget officially.
Okay.
We were a cop,
a scientist, and myself.
The fund was howI could contribute.
How much?
$75,000.
You could rob me blind.
But we're hoping you realize
you can't run from this.
So, can you conher bank, or not?
Good.
Oh, Gemma!
Look, mom, we're crossdressers!
No, you are not.
I'm you!
Oh! You're back.
Felix! Don't go!
Can Felix stay the night, mom?
No!
My work here is done,I'm afraid.
Stay, Felix.
Adios, dragsters.
Wow, okay, so,
the money belongs to Alison.
Mm-hmm.
So what are yougoing to do now?
Are you going torip off your new sis
and abscond with Kira?
She's not my sister and,
yeah, that's exactlywhat we do.
Well.
Shit!
Hide!
You cannot hide inminimalist furniture!
Go!
Shit!
What?
You're not supposed to be here.
Nice.
I thought...
you're stayingat Cody's for a while.
I think that's a good idea!
Well, I think you'rebeing a bitch.
I'm the bigger person, here.
I need a change of clothes.
Uh, I've been reinstated, Paul.
Hey.
Oh.
Well, how do youfeel about that?
What, are youpainting by numbers?
I guess I am.
Okay, I'm sorryI'm like this, Paul.
You're not like this,
Beth, it's your job.
Yeah, but I'ma cop first, Paul,
but, shit.
How would you like itif I started pulling
this schizophrenic hot-and-cold crap on you?
Maybe you should, Paul.
I mean, seriously, whereare we going with this?
Sorry,
got to go.
Oh. My. God.
Oh!
She doesn't want to break up
with big-dick Paul, unh.
He smells it in her musk.
You are stuffed!
Oh, holy shit.
Oh, don't worry, I bethe's wanking already.
Oh, he'd better be.
Oh! Paul, all soapy.
No, no, no, no! Ugh, ah!
Eye on the prize, okay?
Get the money back fromBeth's other partner,
get out.
Maybe it's yourlady-grip walther.
You like your bigGlock, don't ya?
So, two sets of tire tracks
at the crime scene...
one motorcycle and one car?
Yeah, but there had to bethree people there.
So if the killer's ona motorcycle, then, what,
he has an accomplice,
drives the Vic to the quarry?
Or the Vic has a driver,
who doesn't goto police, panics,
and half-ass buries the body?
Yeah, the body dump
doesn't matchthe professional hit.
Exactly.
And I got somethingelse for you, Beth.
You're going to love this.
That was in the sniper's nest.
Yeah, we got a live one.
Phone calls, leaving clues,
messing with us.
Range 7! Weapons down, please!
Det Childs.
Yeah, suzuki?
Okay, hang on a sec.
All clear!
Okay.
Thanks.
Patrol spotted
my stolen suzukidown in parkdale.
It's a long shot,
but may as well seeif the tires match.
Is this the stolen sport bike?
Yeah, it looks like it.
All right,let's find the super.
My son, my son!
Yeah, I know, he's not home,
but the motorcycle,
does it belong to a renter?
Upstairs! My son no here.
Thank you.
I thought you were the onewho's supposed to deal
with the nonenglish-speaking majority.
Yeah, my Ukrainian sucks.
Easy access.
Motorcycle gloves.
It's open.
What you got there?
Uh...
"For you formedmy inward parts;
You knitted metogether in my..."
"Mother's womb. I praise you,
for I am fearfullyand wonderfully made."
Bibles, dolls.
This perp's got some deepseated
spiritual problems.
Art, you're hurt!Art, you're hurt!
Go!
Go? No!
I'm okay! Go!
Go after him! Go!
Shit.
Freeze! Police!
Shit. Shit!
Shit.
Shots fired!
780 bain. Bain and heward!
Foot pursuit in progress.
Art.
Where are you?
I think he went west
between the two...the rowhouses.
I think he went into one
of the abandonedbuildings here.
Beth!
No!
Beth.
Good riddance,
Elizabeth Childs.
I'm not Beth!
Dirty little copy cop.
Who are you?
Ogh!
Not yet, not-Beth.
Beth!
Jesus Christ!
Are you okay?
Hey.
I'm fine, I'm fine.
Where'd he go?
Hey!
Okay, okay, I gotcha.
I gotcha, come on.
All I saw was hoodie.
He hit me from behind.
Then you struggled withhim at close quarters?
Yeah, I was almost out.I never saw his face.
Lieutenant.
I almost lost not one,but two detectives.
How the hell are you inthis without backup, Art?
It was a thread, lieutenant.
It was a flimsy leadon a stolen bike.
Well, it sure hit.
Are you sure you're all right?
I'm fine.
Just let me take her home.
I never should've toldyou to go after him.
Of course I'm going togo after him, Art.
It's not your fault.
No, no, I should'vehad your back.
You had mine.I didn't have yours.
Yes, you did.
Look, shit happens fast, okay?
Will you please?
I'm not going tolet you drive me home
like an invalid, okay?
I just need a showerand an early start
so we can catch this guy, okay?
Hey.
Your money's all there.
You did have it in the trunk.
Sorry I held it over you.
Guess I owe you one.
No, we're square, Art.
Hey, you're not goingto hug me, are ya?
See you in the morning.
Are you sure about this?
Oh, man.
Bloody mrs s. She's right.
Really?
What kind of mother am I
if I snatch my own daughter?
A crap one, I agree.
And if I rob Alison,
run now and never tell my...
Clones?
Oh, God, we do have to find
another word for that.
Don't tell them what,Sarah, what happened?
After all this, you'rereally going to go
and just give the moneyback to bitchface?
Mrs s gave me one visit.
I need to get it right.
Okay, well,
this has taken yearsoff my life.
Now can you please tell me
what in the hellhappened to your face.
Ah.
Ah!