Huxley station.
Shit.
Sorry.
Next stop:Huxley station.
Next train to New York City
will be departingon platform 8B
in 10 minutes.
Next train to New York City,
platform 8B in 10 minutes.
Hey, hey, it's Sarah.
Yeah, I'm back in town.
I want to see Kira, okay?
Well, that's not fair, is it?
Can I at least speak to her?
Hello?
Bitch!
Aah!
Stop the train!Stop the train!
Stop the train!
May I have yourattention, please.
Due to an emergency --
Stand back.Move back!
Get control down here, now!
Elizabeth Childs.
Two phones.
Oh, my God,
you look like crap.
Hi.
Hello.
No, but seriously.
Ew.All right.
How's life, Felix?
This long, no see?You don't get to know.
I didn't miss yourbirthday, did I?
No. I know. It'stotally pedestrian
and the only reason I'm here.
Oi, Bobby.
Hey, Felix.
Guinness?Yeah.
How's Vic the dick?
Yeah, I hit himfirst, this time.
With an ashtray, so...
He's a little blue.
Coke?
It's Vic's.Think you can flip it
to one of yourBay Street blow boys?
You have no ideawhat that costs me.
I'll give you 20%.
I wasn't talkingabout my cut, Sarah.
I was talking about my pride.
What are you up to?
I'm here for Kira, Fe.
After what happened,you really think Mrs S
is going to let you take her?
She's my daughter.She's going to have to.
You've been gonealmost a year, Sarah.
I'm not judging.
I'm just saying.
All right?
Ta.
Yeah, so I'm back on the run,
the usual Sarah shitestorm.
Apparently.
And on that note,something really weird
just happenedat the train station.
What?
I saw a girl kill herself.
Ew!
A jumper?
Yeah, and she looked
exactly like me, Felix.
What you mean?
Oh! You robbedthe body.
No, she left the bagon the platform.
Isn't that essentiallyrobbing her body?
Okay, that's weird.
Yeah, you think?
Elizabeth Childs?
It's you, with a nice haircut.
And a nice address.
What the hell, Fe?Did I have a twin sister?
Well, now, when you'rea poor little
orphan foster wretch,anything's possible.
Or so we tell ourselves.
I'm going to go up to her flat.
Yeah, to find out who she is
or to rob the rest of her shit?
No car. Therehas to be a car.
Is that her phone?
Yeah.Well, answer it.
Try and get 20k for it, yeah?
All right, fine.What about Vic?
I'll call ya.
Okay.Okay?
Okay.
Hello!
Boyfriend.
Squares.
Paul Dierden.
Out of town 'til Saturday.
Well?
Shit for quality.
I'll give you $10,000 for it.
10? With the hayroll?
You can do better.
I'll think about it.
Better think fast.
Okay.
Okay!
Shit!
What?
Where the hell is Sarah?
Shit, Vic!Where is she?
Can't. Breathe.
Oh!
Sarah!
Sarah?!
What the hellis wrong with you?
Where the hell is Sarah?Toodles.
Where is she?!I don't know.
I haven't seen herin, like, a year.
She's been with you.Bullshit!
She's not my problem anymore.
Listen to me, Felix.I'm just going to
ask you once --Where. Is. The. Coke?
Cocaine?
Felix.
All right, fine.
Here.
Blow me.
That's really funny.
What the hell happenedto your head?
Well, let's see --Sarah blindsided me,
then she took offwith the coke.
Listen to me!Listen to me.
Listen!I'm under hook
with Pouchy.Look at me.
You understand?Look at me!
That's going tobring pain on me.
'Til I find her, it's on you.
You mind if I have this?
I'll be back. She betterbe here, fruitcake.
Lovely to see youagain, Victor.
Sarah.
It's "Beth".
So my credit is maxed, but,
I've got a sweet padand my new boyfriend,
Paul's, out of townfor the weekend.
Unfortunately, your realboyfriend, Vic the dick,
is already here.Shit!
Oh, I'm fine,by the way. Thank you.
I'm sorry, Fe.
Your blow is abysmal,by the way.
I'll be lucky to get10k for it.
What?That's not enough.
For what?
To get out, Fe,set ourselves up
with Kira somewhere.
Sarah, who is Elizabeth Childs?
I don't know.
She's just a girlwho looks like me.
A girl with a pretty nice life.
If it's so nice,why'd she kill herself?
Hold on.
Fe, she's got
$75,000 in a savings account.
Say again.
75k!
The account was just opened,
like, 3 weeks ago.
That's enough to losebloody Vic, yeah?
We can get away with this, Fe,
the three of us.
Sarah, any second,someone's going to
I.D. the bodyand it's game over,
so you should really justdrop it all right now.
Nice work with theashtray, by the way.
Vic has stitches.Hello?
I'm standing outsideHuxley station right now --
Shut up.I'm thinking.
As you can see,it's emptying out.
Authorities havecleared out the station
after an unidentified womanfell onto the tracks
and was killed.Now, witnesses aren't sure
how the womancame to be on the tracks
or whether foul playwas involved.
- Fe! - Police have not releasedany more details.
I have an idea.
All right, give me a big smile.I want a big smile.
Why are you shooting me right now?I love shooting you.
Yeah yeah yeah.
¢Ü Live fast,die young ¢Ü
¢Ü bad girls do it well
¢Ü live fast, die young,bad girls do it well ¢Ü
¢Ü my chain hits my chest ¢Ü
¢Ü when I'm bangin'on the dashboard ¢Ü
Oh, shit.
Drugstore --
¢Ü Get back
¢Ü get down
¢Ü pull me closer,if you think you can hang ¢Ü
¢Ü hands up
¢Ü hands high
¢Ü don't go screamin'
are you ready to put your body
through months of hellfor the full?
You're damn right.
¢Ü I'm comin' in theCherokee gasoline ¢Ü
¢Ü There's steamon the window screen ¢Ü
¢Ü take it, take it
¢Ü wheels bouncin'like a trampoline ¢Ü
You're damn right.
You're d-- w--
you're damned --you're damn right.
¢Ü Bad girls do it well
¢Ü live fast, die young,bad girls do it well ¢Ü
Sorry, Art, whoever you are.
I'm gone for good.
You're damn right.
¢Ü My chain hits my chest ¢Ü
¢Ü Back it, back it
¢Ü yeah, pull upto the bumper game ¢Ü
¢Ü with a signal
¢Ü cover me, 'causeI'm changin' lanes ¢Ü
¢Ü had a handle on it
¢Ü my life, I broke it
¢Ü when I getto where I'm goin' ¢Ü
¢Ü gonna have you sayin' it ¢Ü
Hi.
Uh, Beth Childs.
I have an appointmentwith the manager,
Stephen Riggs.
Sure, I'll let himknow you're here.
Ugh! Felix!
Ow!
Use it or hang it up, okay?
Do not snap towelsat me, Bobby.
I had a verytraumatic childhood.
Yeah, hi. Um --
oh, totally awful --
apparently, a girlkilled herself
at Huxley station last night
and I think I know her.
Sarah.Sarah Manning.
Beth?
Hi!
Good to see you again.
How are you?
Yeah, good, Stephen, thanks.
Busy.
I pred last week,at 2:14.
It was only a half,but it almost killed me.
How'd you do, yourlast charity run?
I...don't know,in fact.
I need to makea large withdrawal
from that account.
I see. Right,this is the one
you just opened.
Yeah, I'll leave $500 in,
to keep the account open,
but I need the rest,in cash, please.
Cash?
Yeah.
I'd really recommenda cashier's check, if you...
No, 50s and 100s, please.
Well, we don't keepthat much on hand.
See, anything over $10,000,we have to special-order
and that takes2 to 4 business days.
So...
Stephen,
what could I doto --
to push a rush on that?
You know, 24 hours.
Could I sponsor
your nextcharity-run thing?
You certainly can.Deal.
But...
This card is --
I'm not even sure I'veactivated that yet.
If I did, I need to repin it.
Demagnetized, maybe?Yeah.
You know what?
Let's start with a new one
and then we'll organizethe withdrawal.
Okay.
Do you want access
to your safe depositbox as well?
Oh, yeah.
I'd love that, Stephen.
"Where are you?Must see you".
Yeah, good luck with that.
Alison Hendrix.Elizabeth Childs.
Katja Obinger.
What the hell are you doing?!
Shit.
Get in the car!
Yeah --no, thanks.
Look, get the car, damn it!
What's the charge?
Don't, Beth, not today.
We're late!
Yeah. Okay, yeah.Calm down.
Where were you?
We were going to walkthrough it again.
Uh, yeah, yeah.I got held up.
Don't worry about it.
I worry.Suddenly,
you don't give a damn,I get pissed.
My fat ass is on theline here, too.
Now, you had better be ready.
Are you ready?!
Yeah.Yeah, I'm ready.
You're sure as helloverdressed.
Were you out all night,or something?
No, you know what?Give me a second.
I'll go in and change.
Yeah, right.
You'd probably take offon me again.
Look, Beth, I know this shit is
as hard as it gets,
but you got to stopmaking it worse.
Art.
Just...drive.
Oh, is that her?
Yes, yeah.
Are you okay?
Yeah.Yeah, I'm good.
Okay.
Colin, um --
can I call you Colin?
My mum does.
Ah. Um, well,don't get me wrong --
I usually do enjoycreepy, I do,
it's just, um,
the air in here,is that just me?
Because it smellslike --
Uh, no, it's death.
You can do this, though.
It can be a Gestalt.
Oh, my.
Holy shite.
Let's go.
Hey, good luck, Beth.
"Fashionably late,"you call that?
She's here, lieutenant.
You get busy.Detective, come with me.
Show's over!
Oh.
Stick to your statement
and you'll be fine, okay?
I got to -- I got touse the washroom.
Lieutenant.
All right.
Get yourself sorted.
Detective.
Yeah.
Washroom's this way.
Right.
Felix?Beth is a cop.
I'm a cop, Felix.Abort.
This will be shocking, Felix,
but, for her,it was instant. Okay?
Okay.
Oh, my God!I --
Oh! That's --that --
that's so --
All right, I can't.I can't do it.
You got --I need to --
That's too messed up.I can't.
It's okay.You can lean on me.
All right.
Thank you.
Morgue water.Delicious.
Is it her?
Yeah.
Your sister.I'm very sorry.
Foster sister.
But we were very close.
You know, we spent all our, um,
formative years together.
Right.
Okay, well,there's a few things
you need to sign.
But if you --
if you need -- want --anyone to talk to,
you know,
over a drink or...
Well, aren't you an odd duck.
All right, statement ofofficer Elizabeth Childs,
entering into record her versionof the line-of-duty shooting,
7 October of this year,resulting in
a civilian fatality,one Margaret Chen.
In your own words, please.
Begin by stating your name.
Anytime, detective.
I panicked. What doyou want me to say?
Pretty much anythingbut "I panicked."
I'm kidding.
Where's your wit gone?
You haven't called me"dipshit" all day.
You don't have tobabysit me, dipshit.
I know.
But who else would?
Thanks, doc.See you next week.
Look, Beth,
I know this thing has got you
all twisted up,
but you got toforgive yourself.
Shootings happen.
To whoever's there withthe gun in their hand.
Dr. Bowerswill see you now.
Felix, open the goddamn door!
Felix, I know you're in there!
Open the door, now!
Ooh!
You bastard.
What the hellis wrong with you?
Huh?
Where's Sarah?
Sarah's dead.
I'm sorry, what?
She's dead.
Vic.
She killed herself.
Yeah? Bullshit.Where is she, Felix?
She jumped in front of a train
because youare such an arsehole!
What's this?
Her death certificate.
Bullshit.It's not real.
I identified her body.
Vic, she's dead, she's gone!
Okay, Felix, stop.Stop! Stop it!
She told you to say this?
She's not dead.Where is she?
Stupid bitch.
Sarah.
It's not coming back to you?
Hmm, no, not really.
Uh, I know I shot a civilian.
Maggie Chen,
44, single, churchgoer.
I'm just missing --
Missing what?Explain.
Uh...
Myself? Um --
Yeah, I'm --I glitched,
break, or something.
I think I need some,you know, leave.
You're under suspension.
Right.
Ahem!
See, I'm havingtrouble with detail,
so I'm not sure I shouldsay anything at all.
It's okay.I's all confidential.
Have you shared anyof these dissociations
with Paul?
Yeah, no, we're fine.
I don't want to talkabout Paul.
Paul's away.
No, he's in Cleveland.
Beth,
uh,
a waitress makesa mistake at work.
She, what? Dropsa plate of meatloaf,
doesn't get a tip.
Try to separate "mistake"from "result."
Getting backon the job, for you,
is all about moving forward
from a moment youcan never take back.
You need to talk to meabout that moment.
About seeing cell phoneand reacting "gun".
Mm-hmm.
Can I make another appointment?
So, your twin,
all hopped up on coptranquilizers,
guns down an innocentChinese lady
holding a cell phonein her hand.
Is that true?
I don't know.
I'm not even sureher partner knows.
Feels like she's lyingabout something.
With 75 grand in a new account?
She's well dodgy.
Yeah, whatever she was into,
it drove her bloody nuts, yeah?
Yeah, suicide'sthrilling, agreed.
But, can we get the elephant
out of the room?
What?
Well, look at her.
You're related.
This could be your story.
It's not.
Every foster kid dreamsof their lost family.
Oh, my God.
Deep down, we allhope we're special.
Yeah, the last thingI am is special.
If that was my boyfriend,
I'd jump in frontof a train, too.
Don't say that.
Paul's hot and you know it.
Oh, Vic is keening
like a banshee.He wants a funeral.
You can't have a funeral.
The whole sad point is
nobody would notice if I died.
What's this?Birth certificates?
Alison Hendrix,
Beth.
Katja Obinger.Born in Berlin.
Sarah, their birthdates are all
within a month of yours.
It's a coincidence.
I don't care.
It's just a score, Fe.
Let me finish whatI started and then
I'll come backfor you and Kira, yeah?
Oh.
You're going todisappear again?
Yeah, I have to, Fe.
There's dangerous shitin this life.
Somebody keeps texting her.
Oh, texting. My God,how terrifying.
Look, Fe, sell the coke
and keep half the money
and give the otherhalf to Kira, yeah?
You left Kirawith Mrs S overnight
and you didn't come back
for 10 months!
I'm trying to fix it.
Tell it to the angels, Sarah.
You're already dead.
Shit!
Beth!
Beth.
Hi.
Hey.
The clash?
Oh, yeah.Uh --
"London Calling."
The clash rock.
Yeah, but you don't.
Are you going somewhere?
Uh...
Uh...no.Just gym stuff.
Weren't you coming backon the weekend?
Well, I wanted to be here.
So?
Yeah?
How was the hearing?
Oh. Uh,I couldn't do it.
I couldn't do it.
You skipped it?
No, um --
I...got sickto my stomach.
I basically puked on them.
Are you serious?
Yeah.
Don't worry.I'm okay.
Beth,
what's happened?
A lot.
Yeah, I know,but you're --
I'm what?
What'd you do to your hair?
Uh...nothing.
I got it cut.
It's longer.
It's just wet.
Something's different.
Bedroom.
Ah!
Right here.
Felix.
For crying out loud.
I'm sorry, man. I don'tknow where else to go.
The men's shelter?
What the hell happenedto your face?
I got in a fight.
Why, Vic?
Why are you such a dick?
I don't know.I'm angry.
Can I come in?
No!
Thanks.
I can't sleep.
I keep seeing her face.
Yeah, me too.
Her pretty face.
Felix,
you and me, we have todo something.
There's just nogoddamn closure, bro.
We have to have, like, a...
a memorial sendoff,or something.
Okay, Vic.
We'll have a wake.
Really? See, that's whatI'm talking about, man,
coming together.
Yeah. Cremation'stoday. I'm buying.
Oh, shit. Yeah,it can't be today.
I got to call Glennand that bitch Sherry
and all her Montreal connects
are going to want to be there.
No no, locals only, Vic.Fast and light,
all right?It's going to be
an intimate memorial pissup.
Okay.Come on, let's go.
Can I...?Okay! That's --
Thank you.
All right, um --
you know what?First, though,
you need a shower and a Xanax.
Okay.
Mmm.Ah! Oh.
For real?
That was amazing.
Was it?
We haven't had that action
for, like, 2 years.
Uh,
I got up for the gym, Paul.
Okay.
Well, you want to tell me
what happened at the hearing?
Uh, I choked, I guess.
They reconvenein a couple days.
Don't worry about it.
Beth.
Hmm? What?
Are you back on the meds?
No.
Then you didn't choke.
You're just finallyfeeling something.
Feeling like the real you.
I got up for the gym.
Are you driving today?
What?
Can I borrow the keysto your car?
Use your own car.
I can't find my keys.
Did you check the thingwhere they always are?
Yeah. Yeah,I checked the thing
where they always are.
Mm.
Okay.
Nice.
Felix!
We can't part angry this time.
It's not goodfor your skin, okay?
Call me, or I'll squeezeyour bloody bollocks
in a vise,you little --
Everything all right?
Yeah. ObnoxiousEnglish relative.
Oh.
Well, I've got your cash.
I just needyour signature here.
Okay.
Right, then.
All done.
Here.
Okay. Good luckwith that run.
Fe?
Felix.
You little shit.
Sarah had a big heart.
It was always fightor flight with her.
You guys rememberhow she was, right?
This is all based on facts.
She was the kind ofperson you want to hang
on to, but she wouldnot be held, would she?
Sarah, I'm sorry.
I know I have a lotto answer for.
My favorite moment --
So,
is it heaven or hell?
I didn't want a funeral,for this very reason, Fe.
Well, you can't do much aboutthat when you're dead, can you?
I'm watching right now.
Really?Oh, well.
Pathetic.
Let me ask you --
I dressed Vic.How do we look?
Yeah, not as goodas Rockabilly Bob.
I know! Still Rockabilly,after all these years.
Got to respect that.
I want to sayshe was like an angel
that was puton earth --
Sherry's upset,though, in't she?
Oh, yeah, she thinksVic pushed you
in front of the train.
It's priceless, really.
Eh, I got the money, Fe.
I still want us to be together.
It can work, yeah?
This is our chance,for me, you, and Kira
to start over.Sarah, I --
Felix, do you mind?!I'm trying to --
Do you want us to goand come back?
Shit. I'm sorry, I -- Vic'sgetting mad. I got to go.
Could you hang up your phone?Oh, shit!
What?
Mrs S is there, Fe.
Shit.
Stop! Stop! Stop!
Oh, shit.
No no no, Fe.
Oh, shit!
Ohh.
No Fe, Kira's there.
Uh --
she can't think I'm dead, Fe.
Fe?
Oh, my God, she can'tthink I'm dead.
Beth.
Beth, why don't you respond
to me?
Beth.
Just keep away from me.
Beth, it's Katja.
Oh, my God.Holy shit.
Why no meeting, Beth?What happening?
Uh --
I brought the briefcase, ja?
The sample foryour friend, Beth.
I was careful, like you said.
Yeah, just stay back.
I'm Katja.Katja Obinger, Beth.
Yeah, I get it,the German, okay?
I've seen yourbirth certificate.
Ja, you asked for it,for proof.
Please, I need to see
your scientist friend, Beth.
Uh, I can't help you.
Get out of the car!
Why are you doing this?
Your partner, hewas following you.
You were the onein the black car?
The open that flashedyour lights.
Ja.
You need to go.
You're police, Beth.We need you.
Don't!
Get out.
Just one.I'm a few.
No family, too.Who am I?
You are not Beth.
Aah!
Oh, God! Shit!
Shit!
Shit.
Hello.
This is not Sarah.
It's not Sarah.
We've been here before.
No, Paul, we definitelyhaven't been here before.
Shit!
Hey, hey!Whoa, whoa, take it easy!
Are you wearing a wire?
When is mummy coming?
Sarah! Sarah!
Aah!